OP
Our long sought-after new member has finally arrived to join us at the Light Music Club.
軽音楽部に待望の入部希望者がやってきました
Welcome to the Light Music Club!
ようこそ 軽音部へ
Hey, don't just stand there.
ほら こっちこっち
Sit down.
座って
All right, now tell us, what's your name?
お名前は何ていうの？
Um, My name is Azu--
あッ 中野です
So what instrument do you play?
パートは何やってんの？
Well, I play--
あッ えっと…
So what's your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は？
What's your favorite color?
Calm down, people.
落ち着け お前ら
CHATTING NOW
Chatting Now
It's really noisy
Never Ending Girls' Talk
ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
We can't wait until the bell
rings at the end of class
終業チャイムまで待てない
Even if we're late,
leaving early is a
遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
No no!
study
精一杯Study After School
hard
We'll
after
School
ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Our hearts won't stop thumping
Our thoughts are going on full throttle
Hope
Desire
Suffering
Wrap them all up with a ribbon
希望·欲望·煩悩　リボンかけて包装
ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New　Type　Version打ち込み
We'll gather lots of data
and put it in a new type version
男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
We have a photo album without guys
and a diary written with love
スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
If we cut our skirts
by 2 centimeters,
we can fly
Further than yesterday
We'll reach a higher octave
than the day before
昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Jumping
now
Jumping Now
ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
It's beautiful
Never     Ending
Girls'     Life
We're looking
forward
to the daily
concert
日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
going to bed
early is a
Even if we
get up early,
早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
No no!
Shouting with all
目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
W
e've
got
Hooray
It's splendid
ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Never Ending
Girls' Song
午後ティータイムには持ってこい
The afternoon
tea  time
is perfect
Our unrequited
L
O
V
E
will be defeated
片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
But here we go!
We'll
sing
for
you
歌えばShining After School
After school
Um, I'm Azusa Nakano, year 1, class 2.
えっと １年２組の中野梓といいます
And I play a little bit of guitar.
パートはギターを少し
Hey, just like Yui does, huh?
あッ 唯と一緒だな
I look forward to playing with you, Yui senpai.
よろしくお願いします 唯先輩
Yui senpai?!
唯先輩…
Senpai, Senpai!
先輩～先輩！
Hey, come back to planet earth.
おーい 帰ってこーい
New Club Member!
For starters, try playing something for us!
とりあえず 何か弾いてみせて
I'm still a beginner, so I'm not very good yet.
まだ初心者なので下手ですけど
No problem! I'm gonna teach you everything I know.
大丈夫 私が教えてあげるから
Wow, you're starting to act like a senpai already.
おおッ 早くも先輩風吹かせてるな
Well, here goes...
そッ それじゃあ…
S-She is great.
うッ うまい
She is way better than I am.
私より断然
あッ あれ？
Uh-oh. What should I do? They are acting all strange all of a sudden.
どうしよう 何だか変な雰囲気
I bet it was because I played so badly.
やっぱり私の演奏が 下手だったから…
I'm so sorry. My playing must have been awful to listen to...
ごめんなさい やっぱり聞き苦しかったですよね
No, that's not why we reacted like that!
ああ いや そういうわけじゃ…
You have a ways to go!
まッ まだまだね
ええ？！
What's with you?
ちょッ 唯
Yui, how long are you gonna keep acting cocky?
おい いつまで見栄張ってるんだよ
Yui senpai! I would really love to hear you play the guitar again.
私 もう一度 唯先輩のギターが聴きたいです
えッ？ ああ～ ええと…
Well...
I threw my back out during the show, so maybe a little later, okay?
ライブで ギックリ腰になったから また今度ね
Lame...
苦しい
Whatever, just move it.
もういいから どいてろ
Well, in any event, I guess we can assume you're going to be joining the club, right?
とにかく 入部してくれるっていうことで いいんだよね？
Yes! I was very moved and excited when I heard you all play at the welcoming ceremony.
はい
新歓ライブの皆さんの演奏を聴いて 感動しました
I look forward to playing with you.
これから よろしくお願いします
She's so dazzling, I can't even look at her...
まぶしすぎて直視できません
Oh, that's right.
あッ そうだ
My application form.
入部届です
Duly received and accepted.
確かに受け取ったから
So, we'll see you here tomorrow then?
明日から よろしくね
You will. I guess I'd better get going now.
はい それじゃあ失礼します
Oh, no! What am I gonna do?!
わッ 私 どうしよう
Go start practicing.
練習しとけ
Hello, everyone!
こんにちは
あッ 元気いっぱいだな
Someone's awfully cheery.
Yes, the end of the school day couldn't come fast enough.
はい 放課後が待ち遠しかったです
Let's get to it then.
それじゃあ 早速…
To practice you mean?
練習ですか？
No, have tea.
お茶にするか
ええッ？
Here's a cup for you, Azusa.
梓ちゃんも どうぞ
Are you sure? I mean, is it okay for us to have tea in the Music Room like this?
あッ あの～ 音楽室でこんなことして大丈夫なんですか？
Yeah, don't sweat it. It's fine.
大丈夫 大丈夫
Um, Ma'am, this isn't my...
あの あの これは…
I'll have milk with my tea.
私 ミルクティーね
ええッ
I'm Miss Yamanaka, your advisor. Nice to meet you.
顧問の山中さわ子です よろしくね
Um, it's nice to meet you, too.
よッ よろしくお願いします
きッ きれいな人だなあ
Wow, she sure is pretty.
I think she'd look good in cat ears.
猫耳とか似合いそうね
Have some sweets, too.
お菓子もどうぞ
Sure!
はーい
They look just as good as always!
今日もおいしそう
So, you have a new member. Spring has come, all right?
それにしても新入部員か 春ね～
Um, Mugi-chan, what's this called?
So, did you get yourself a boyfriend yet?
It's called a Dobos torte.
春になって彼氏できました？
余計なお世話よ ほっといて
Don't bring that up! It's none of your business.
All right, sorry.
This IS the Light Music Club, isn't it?
ここ 軽音部だよね
Oh, maybe they're testing me to see if I have initiative.
もしかして 私の自主性が試されてるのかな
QUIET!
うるさーーい！
ええッ？
Miss Yamanaka, you moron!
さわちゃんのアホーッ！
I just... I just wanted to enjoy my tea in peace...
だって 静かにお茶したかったんだもん
Maybe, but there's a right way to say it.
言い方ってもんがあるだろ
Hey, sorry. Miss Yamanaka is a little bit strange.
ごめんな あの先生ちょっと変なの
Heard that.
おい
Don't let her get to you.
気にしないでね
C'mon, let's eat some cake!
さあ ケーキ食べよう
Teatime is our main selling point, after all.
ティータイムがウチのウリだから
Azusa-chan?
梓ちゃん？
こんなんじゃダメですーッ！
It's not supposed to be like this!
She's flipped out!
わッ キレたッ
I don't sense any motivation from any of you!
皆さん やる気が感じられないです
Um, well, our welcome show was over, so...
えッ いや 新歓終わったあとだったし
That has nothing to do with it!
そんなの関係ありません
It's wrong for you to treat the music room as your personal property!
音楽室を私物化するのも よくないと思います
You should get rid of all these tea sets!
ティーセットは全部 撤去すべきです
No, please anything but that!
それだけは勘弁して
You're a teacher! How can you say that?!
何で先生が言うんですかッ
Look, let's all calm down and just--
まあ とにかく落ち着いて
How do you expect me to be calm, huh?!
これが落ち着いていられますか！
That's a good girl.
いい子 いい子
Petting her isn't gonna calm her--
そんなことで収まるはず…
It calmed her down!
収まったーッ
I'm so sorry I lost my composure.
取り乱して すみませんでした
ううん 全然気にしてないから
That's okay. We don't mind at all.
That's a problem too...
それはそれで…
No, Azusa. You have a very good point.
梓が言うことも一理あるよ
We really ought to show a little more motivation around here.
私達も もっとやる気出していかないと
Are we clear on that?!
わかりましたねッ
Yeah...
はーい
Sign: A few days later
I don't really want to go, not after that scene I caused...
この前 迷惑かけたから 行きたくないなあ
Hi, everyone...
こんにちは…
They aren't fazed at all...
全然 動じてない
W-We were all just about to start band practice! Honest, we were!
いッ 今から 練習するところだったんだよ
ホントだよ
That was fast!
はやッ
I just don't have any energy if I don't eat some cake...
やっぱケーキ食べないと力が出ないよ～
Here, have a bite.
はい 唯ちゃん
あーん
She's good!
うまい！
Why don't you have some, Azusa-chan? It's really good.
梓ちゃんも食べてみなよ おいしいよ
はい あーん
Say "Ah"!
Go on!
ほれ
Tasty...
おいしい
うん 何だって？
What did you say?
I said "wasty"! A waste!
「おしい」って言ったんです
I guess she really didn't like it.
気に入らなかったか～
Try this.
ほい
Try it.
Interesting.
おもろい
Good bye, Miss Yamanaka!
先生 さようなら
Good bye, girls.
はい さようなら
[Sigh]
No more after-school tea time in the music room after today...
今日から音楽室でのティータイムはなしか
Nevertheless, I must act like a teacher...!
でも 教師らしくちゃんとしなきゃ
...once in a while.
たまには…
Hi, girls, are you practicing really hard?
みんな 練習 頑張ってる？
Oh, come on! You're eating!
…って食べてるじゃん！
Now, I can die happy...
私 もうここで死んでもいい
Please don't.
死ぬな
So, tell me, why did you decide against getting rid of all these tea sets?
そういえば
結局 何で ティーセット撤去しなかったの？
Well, because...
そッ それは…
I thought it would be wrong of me to reject everything since I knew.
なんッ 何でもかんでも否定するのは ダメだと思って
へえ～
So, when did you start playing guitar, Azusa-chan?
梓ちゃんって いつギター始めたの？
Um, Let's see, around fourth grade, I guess.
あッ えっと 小４くらいからです
My parents play in a jazz band, so I was really influenced by that.
親がジャズバンドをやっていたので その影響で
へえ～
That means you're not a beginner at all!
全然 初心者じゃないじゃん
I'm curious what it was that got you interested in playing guitar, Yui senpai?
あッ 唯先輩がギター始めた きっかけって何ですか？
W-Who, me?!
えッ 私？
I can't say it!
言えない 軽音が軽い感じの音楽だと思ってたなんて言えない
I can't tell her I joined because I thought the club played lighthearted music!
あッ あの…
Yeah, anyway, it sure is great that a new member's joined the club!
いや とにかく新入部員が入ってよかった
She dodged it!
ごまかした！
Almost forgot. I brought a welcome-to-the-club present for you, Azusa-chan.
そうそう 私 梓ちゃんにプレゼント持ってきたんだった
Ta-dah!
パンパカパーン！
So, what exactly are those?
あの… これ 何ですか？
They're a set of cat ears, of course.
何って 猫耳だけど
I can see that. That's not what I meant.
いや それはわかるんですけど…
What am I supposed to do with them?
えっと これを どうすれば…
フッフッフッ
It's okay, don't worry. It's kind of a Light Music Club ritual.
あッ 大丈夫だよ 軽音部の儀式みたいなもんだから
What kind of ritual?!
何の儀式ですか？
Goodness, you embarrass so easily.
もう 恥ずかしがりやさんねえ
Of course I do!
当たり前です 先輩方だって恥ずかしいですよね？
The rest of you think this is embarrassing too, right?
So?
どう？
Looks great!
似合う～
あッ さすがムギだな
That's our Mugi, all right!
Huh?! Am I the odd one out here?
あれ 私がおかしいの？
Here. Now it's your turn, Azusa-chan.
はい 次 梓ちゃんの番
わあッ
おお～ッ
They look awesome on you!
すごく似合ってるよ
When it comes to this stuff, I'm never wrong.
私の目に狂いはなかったわ
The Light Music Club welcomes you!
軽音部へようこそ！
This was it?!
ここで？
Azusa-chan, you're so cute, you know that?
梓ちゃん かわいい～
Try something like a cat, "Nya" like that.
ニャーって言ってみて ニャーって
ニッ… ニャー
N-Nya...
ああ～ッ
I couldn't help it!
はッ つい…
That's it. Your nickname has to be Azu-nyan!
あだ名は あずにゃんで決定だね
えッ
あッ あの…
けいおん！
おお～ッ
Next, put on this outfit! You'll be a cat-eared maid!
次は この服よ
ネコミミメイド
No way! Absolutely not!
それは 絶対イヤです
But it'll look great!
似合うのに～
I won't!
イヤですッ
Azusa is so cute.
梓 かわいいな
It's great that the object of their teasing is Azusa now instead of me.
いじられる対象が 私から梓に移ったのは助かったけど
But this loneliness that I'm feeling...
でも この寂しい気持ちは
What is it?
何？
What the heck have you been talking about?
さっきから何言ってるのよ
あーッ 楽しかった
That was so fun!
I'm exhausted even though we didn't practice at all.
練習もしてないのに疲れました
Oops, I forgot something back up in the music room.
あッ 私 音楽室に忘れ物
Okay, we'll go on ahead, then.
じゃあ 先 行ってるな
Yeah, okay.
ああ うん
There it is.
あった あった
A mustache!
ヒッ ヒゲ
That's lame, Mio.
苦しいぞ～
You know, Azu-nyan. There's a fantastic ice cream shop really near where my house is.
ねえ あずにゃん
ウチの近くに おいしいアイス屋さんがあるんだよ～
Why don't we all go there?
みんなで行きましょう
Great idea! It'll be my treat!
先輩が おごってあげる
あッ はあ…
Okay.
No, no. You have to answer "Nya", okay?
違う違う 返事はニャーだよ
See? "Nya".
はい ニャー
N-Nya!
ニャッ ニャー
ゴロゴロゴロ
She's being domesticated?!
手なづけられている
This is great!
おいしい～ッ
It's delicious, all right.
ホントにおいしい
You've got some on your cheek.
アイス ついてるぞ
Are you okay? Do you think you can handle our club?
大丈夫？軽音部やっていけそう？
Yeah, I guess...
あッ えっと
It's just to me the relaxed atmosphere is kinda... you know.
こののんびりした空気がちょっとアレですけど
まあ…
It's okay. You'll get used to it.
大丈夫 すぐ慣れるよ
I don't exactly want to.
ていうか 慣れたくない…
Sign: Emergency meeting in progress! Do not enter!!
So, what's the emergency meeting about?
何？ 緊急会議って
We have a brand-new member.
新入部員が入ったのに
So I think we're asking for trouble if we keep goofing off like this all the time.
いつまでも まったりダラダラしてたらまずいと思うんだよな
Y-You do?
そッ そうなの？
If we keep this up, Azusa might get tired of it and quit!
このままじゃ 梓 辞めてしまうかもしれないぞ
I don't wanna Azu-nyan to stop coming!
あずにゃんがいなくなるのはイヤだ
Then we've no choice. We have to find some dirt on...
仕方ない 何か梓の弱み…痛い！
Ow!
Maybe we should try coming up with a proper activities plan.
ちゃんと活動計画を立てた方がいいんじゃないか？
An activities plan?
活動計画？
She has a point. For starters...
確かにな～ じゃあまず…
Let's throw a welcome party for Azusa!
梓の歓迎会をするか
Good idea!
いいね～
Sounds like fun!
楽しそう
Wait a minute!
おい！
Board: Lucky boat fare rates
C'mon, Azu-nyan, eat up. There is plenty!
ほら あずにゃんも食べて食べて
We have cake, too.
ケーキもあるわよ
And I brought this for you!
梓には これッ
Cut that out!
コラーッ！
You like taiyaki?
たい焼き 好きなの？
Hm.
うん
Hey! Watch where you're throwing, you idiot!
こら どこ投げてんだよッ
You can do it, Ritchan!
頑張れ りっちゃーん
Mio is a great bassist. So why is she in such an unmotivated club?
澪先輩は うまいのに
何でこんな やる気のない部活にいるんだろう
What is it?
何？
Um, Nothing.
いッ いえ
Um, Mio? Do you play in any bands outside the Light Music Club?
あッ あの… 澪先輩は外でバンド組んだりしないんですか？
Huh, playing in a band outside the club would be fun, all right.
うーん 確かに外バンも おもしろそうだよね
Oh, are you sure you wanna be saying things like that?
あ～ そんなこと言っていいのかな
W-What's that a picture of?!
何よ それッ
Let me see it! What is it?!
Is she being blackmailed into staying?
よッ 弱み 握られてるのかな？
The bunny look works, too.
バニーも いいわね
あッ さわちゃん先生
Hi, Miss Yamanaka!
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
遅れて ごめんね
I had a few things to get together first.
いろいろと仕込みがあってさ
Ta-dah!
ジャーン！
It's so sweets!
かわいい～
Yeah, awesome as always.
あいかわらず スゲエな
Azu-nyan, if you don't wanna wear them, we'll be happy to.
あずにゃん
嫌なら私達が着るから
That's not the problem...
そッ そういう問題じゃ…
That was so much fun!
楽しかったね
So, where should we go next time?
今度は どこ行くかな
Why don't we go to the zoo?
動物園とか
Hot spring would be nice, too.
温泉もいいわね
Oh, good idea!
ああッ それいい！
Yes, it's a wonderful idea!
ホント すごく素敵です
You think so? You really wanna go to one next time?
えッそう？じゃあ今度ホントに行っちゃう？
Listen up, everyone!
みんな聞いてッ
We are the Light Music Club!
ウチは軽音部だから
Starting tomorrow, we're gonna practice. Is that clear?
明日からは 絶対 練習するからな
No if's, and's, or but's, you got it?!
絶対の絶対の絶対！
Sign: Preparation room
Okay, we're supposed to be the Light Music Club even though you may have all forgotten.
みんな 忘れてるかもしれないが
ウチは軽音部だから
Yeah, well, I remember just fine.
いや 忘れてないから
Today, we're gonna practice!
今日は練習するぞ！
Yeah!
オーッ！
Y-Yeah...
オー？
Okay, now. Since we have Yui and Azusa on guitar now, that'll widen our range quite a bit.
よし 唯と梓 ギターが２人になったから
演奏の幅が広がるな
Who wants to play lead guitar?
どっちがリードギターやる？
Well, the lead guitar should be--
それは もちろん先輩が…
Me! Me! I wanna do it!
はいはい 私がやる
Where's this confidence coming from?
この自信は どこから？
一応 ２人の演奏を聴いてみてから 決めた方が…
I suppose it would make more sense to decide after we hear you both play.
Um, I guess I'll go first then...
そッ それじゃ 私から
Azusa is terrific.
すごい 梓ちゃん
She's a great player.
やっぱり うまいな
Okay, now you--
次は唯の番…
Huh?!
I threw out my back...
ギックリ腰が…
Give it a rest, already.
いいかげんにしろ
Azu-nyan, please teach me how to play guitar!
あずにゃん ギター教えてください
Wow, she is quick on her feet!
変わり身 はえーな
あッ そこはミュートした方が…
I think you should use muting on that part.
And I think that last phrase would sound better with a little vibrato.
あと さっきのフレーズは ビブラートきかせるといいかも
Muting? Vibrato? What are those?
ミュート？ ビブラート？
何それ？
Huh?!
Believe it or not, she's been playing for a year now.
こんなんでも １年間やってきたんだ
How can she get by without knowing muting and vibrato?
ミュートもビブラートも知らずに どうやって…
Hey, wait? She is using muting just fine.
あれ？ ちゃんとミュートできてる
Oh, that's what you call that. So that's muting?
ああ さっきのが ミュートっていうんだ
Muting is a fingering technique where you lightly touch the strings to dampen the notes as you play them.
Sign: Sawa-chan Memo
ミュートとは 弦に軽く触れて 音が伸びないようにする技術よ
Yui is the type of person who doesn't read the manual when she buys a game.
唯はゲーム買っても 説明書読まないタイプなんだよ
I can see that.
納得です
Could you please put some royal milk tea on for me?
じゃあ そろそろ ロイヤルミルクティー いれてくれる？
Oh, I'm sorry. But today we only gotta practice.
あの 今日は練習しますから
I suppose we can take a little break.
ちょっとだけ休憩するか
ほげ～～
What about practice?!
練習はッ？
ああ～明日から 頑張ろう
We'll work harder starting tomorrow.
Azu-nyan!
あずにゃん あーん
You say "Ah".
はい あーん
I have a special cup just for you, Azusa-chan.
はい 梓ちゃん専用のカップよ
はッ ダメになる
This will ruin me. If I stay here, it will ruin me!
このままじゃ ダメになる
I should play in other bands outside the Light Music Club.
軽音部じゃなくて
よそのバンドに参加しよう
There have to be other great bands out there.
他にもきっと 素敵なバンドが…
I don't get it.
どうしてだろう
All these other bands are better than the Light Music Club.
どのバンドも ウチの軽音部より うまいのに
So why?
どうして？
Sign: Preparation room
Azu-nyan hasn't come in a while...
最近 あずにゃん 来ないね
She might not come back...
もう来ないかもな
Azusa! Why haven't you come to the club lately?
あッ 梓
何で最近 こなかったんだよ
We've been practicing every day since you were here last!
ここんとこ 毎日練習してたんだぞ
We've been waiting for you to come back!
待ってたよ
Something wrong?
どうした？
You didn't come just tell us that you're quitting?
まさか 辞めるって言いにきたのか？
No way, please anything but that!
それだけは勘弁してくだせえ
I don't know anymore...
わからなくなって
えッ？
I don't know why I wanted to join your club anymore...
どうして軽音部に 入ろうと思ったのか
But why your show touched me so much in a way that it did.
どうして新歓ライブの演奏に あんなに感動したのか
I thought that I could figure it out if I hung around you for a little while but--
しばらく一緒にいてみればきっとわかると思って やってきたけど
I just don't know anymore!
けど やっぱりわからなくって
Azu-nyan...
あずにゃん…
Right!
よし じゃあ 梓のために演奏するか
Let's play a number for Azusa, then!
Let's make her remember what she was feelings that day, Okay?
そのときの気持ちを 思い出せるようにさ
うん！
Yui-senpai hardly knows any musical lingo at all.
唯先輩は まるで音楽用語知らないし
Ritsu's drumming is always kind of wild.
律先輩のドラムも 走り気味なのに
So why are their songs so good when the four of them play together?
４人そろって演奏すると
どうしてこんなにいい曲になるんだろう
Why?
どうして？
Azusa.
梓
You asked me the other day why I don't play in bands outside the club, remember?
この前 何で私が外バン組まないか聞いたよね
Yeah.
はい
I think it's because I love being in a band with these girls.
やっぱり 私はこのメンバーとバンドするのが楽しいんだと思う
えッ？
I bet the others feel the same.
きっと みんなもそうで
I think that's why we all play so well together.
だからいい演奏になるんだと思う
C'mon! Play a song with us, Azusa!
さあ 一緒にやろう 梓
All right! I really wanna play music with you guys, I really do!
はい 私 やっぱり先輩方と演奏したいです
What a relief!
よかった～ッ
Now, I know there's gonna be time that we're gonna slack off and drink tea or whatever.
まあ これからも お茶飲んだりダラダラすることもあると思うけど
But I think that time is crucial for us.
それもやっぱり 必要な時間なんだよ
うん
I'm so burned out...
燃え尽きた
I don't think I'm gonna wanna play for at least a whole week...
向こう１週間は演奏したくねえ～
本当に？
Are they serious?
Probably...
多分
Azu-nyan, why don't you try on those cat ears?
あずにゃん 猫耳つけてみて
What? No way!
イヤです
Please, it'll make me try harder!
ねえ お願い そしたら頑張れるから
Umm...
えッ じゃあ…
The power of cute compels you!
萌え萌え キュン～
Please
don't say
"you are
lazy,"
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
I am
actually
crazy
だって本当はcrazy
The swans
are actually
白鳥たちはそう　見えないとこでバタ足するんです
kicking their legs
hard out
of sight
Being true and sincere to my instincts,
I accept that I'll
be tossed around
本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
The path ahead looks bright
前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I
take rests
sometimes
近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut,
it's the easy way out
If I have wings to use, then it'll be the best
ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Crap, I broke a nail!
I'll fix it with glue
That's enough to give me
a sense of achievement
それだけでなんか達成感
大事なのは自分　かわいがること
What's important is to take good care of yourself
自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
If you can't love yourself, then you can't love someone else
Please
don't
say
you
are
Please don't say「You are lazy」
because
you
are
actually
だって本当はcrazy
Capable
hawks
能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
hide their picks
out of sight
I try to use my imagination,
想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
but reality is a bitch
I'm still just learning,
発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
so I'll be out of pitch sometimes
Next Episode
It must be rough to be a teacher, and working during summer break.
夏休みなのに 大変ですねえ
Yeah, we have to go to seminars and whatnot...
研修とか いろいろあってねえ
Are you guys practicing?
あなた達も練習？
Yeah.
はい
Did you want something?
何か用？
The Light Music Club is gonna have a training camp.
軽音部で合宿するんだけど
And we were all wondering if you wanted to come?
先生も 来るかなあと思って
A training camp, huh?
合宿ねえ
She doesn't look too thrilled about it, does she?
はは…めんどくさそうな顔
Aren't we ever gonna get around to practicing?
ちゃんと練習できるのかなあ
Azu-nyan!
あずにゃ～ん
Another Training Camp!
Gimme the cabbage!
キャベツ うめーッ